Alright, an easy way to check your
headings is to go to the View ribbon and
click on the Show Navigation Pane. This
will pop up on the left-hand side of your
screen all of your headings in your
document. And you can click on each one,
the mobile app, right? Okay, download,
good, sign in. Next one is, wait a minute,
that shouldn't be a heading. That should
be regular text. So I go under Styles and
it's actually, this text paragraph should
be Normal. So I now click on Normal and
then I continue on. Bookshare, click on
the next one, yep, log in. Oh, wait a
minute, what's this blank? Ah, again, this
was a heading two, that shouldn't be,
change it to Normal. And then my last
heading, Upload for new materials.
Perfect.